Register of the Joan Kennedy Taylor papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Writing and Publishing File, 1961-2001
  - Writing by Others, 1977-2000
    - "Defending Pornography," by Nadine Strosser, 1992 (Text : 27: 5)
- Sound Recordings, 1959-1999
  Composed of sound cassettes with recordings from various interviews, courses, conferences, and conventions attended by Joan Kennedy Taylor. Some of the tapes bear the same titles as articles and monographs that were written by Joan Kennedy Taylor. The series also includes Byline broadcast recordings. The major of tapes in the series are compact sound cassettes, with a few micro compact sound cassettes.
  - Ayn Rand (Original), February 7 - April 16, 1959 (Text : 28: 1)
  - Ayn Rand (Copy), February 7 - April 14, 1959 (Text : 28: 2)
  - Byline (weeks 51 and 52), December 12-23, 1983 (Text : 28: 3)
  - Camille Paglia, September 27, 1997 (Text : 28: 4)
  - Charles Murray, circa 1980 (Text : 28: 5)
  - Charles Murray Interview, circa 1980 (Text : 28: 6)
  - Charles Murray Tape, circa 1980 (Text : 28: 7)
  - Charles Murray, In Pursuit, (Cato Summer Seminar), 1987 (Text : 28: 8)
  - Charles Murray, "The Pursuit of Happiness," (Cato's Third Annual Pulic Policy Day), 1986 (Text : 28: 9)
  - Free Inquiry 1990 Conference (Session 4 tape 1 Side A - Feminism, African American), 1997 (Text : 28: 10)
  - Free Inquiry 1990 Conference (Session 4 tape 2 Side A - Feminism, African American) (Text : 28: 11)
  - Free Inquiry 1990 Conference (Session 7 tape 1 Side A - Humanism, Libertarianism, Altruism) (Text : 28: 12)
  - Free Inquiry 1990 Conference (Session 7 tape 2 Side A - Humanism, Libertarianism, Altruism) (Text : 28: 13)
  - Free Inquiry 1990 Conference (Session 7 tape 3 Side A - Humanism, Libertarianism, Altruism) (Text : 28: 14)
  - Free Markets and Human Potential, 1992 (Text : 28: 15)
  - "Give us the Tools,", circa 1980 (Text : 28: 16)
  - "Guy Lebow at Large,", August 13, 1992 (Text : 28: 17)
  - "The Influence of Ayn Rand," Barbara Branden, April 22, 1999 (Text : 28: 18)
  - Interview with David Kelly, circa 1990 (Text : 28: 19)
  - Interview with Lee Nason, August 24, 1997 (Text : 28: 20)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylor, Dawn's Early Light III Speaker, September 5, 1993 (Text : 28: 21)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylor, Kathleen Dunn, Libertarian Feminism, April 29, 1994 (Text : 28: 22)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylor, Libertarian Feminism, New York Libertarian Party, 1990 (Tape : 28: 23)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylor at LPQC (side A only), October 18, 1997 (Text : 28: 24)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylor, "Porno. - Is Censorship the Answer?", October 25, 1986 (Text : 28: 25)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylor, Respecting Diversity New York Libertarian Convention, 1981 (Text : 28: 26)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylpr on WBAT (LP Convention Interview), September 2, 1983 (Text : 28: 27)
  - Joan Kennedy Taylor, Women in the Free Society, Libertarian International, Stockholm, 1986 (Text : 28: 28)
  - Libertarian Mind - JKT Boston, March 31, 1979 (Text : 28: 29)
  - Libertarian Party Mass Talk - on getting libertarian ideas spread, circa 1980 (Text : 28: 30)
  - "The New Law of Sexual Harassment: Everything you know is Wrong,", circa 1980 (Text : 28: 31)
  - Reagan's First Six Months (Burt/ Taylor/ Richman/ Hospers/ Friedman), circa 1980 (Text : 28: 32)
  - Rita Risser, May 18, 1998 (Text : 28: 33)
  - A Service of Remembrance for Bea Hessen, December 23, 1989 (Text : 28: 34)
  - Suzanne Riggenbach, May 17, 1998 (Text : 28: 35)
  - "What To Do About Sexual Harassment with out Calling Cops,", May 18, 1996 (Text : 28: 36)
  - What You Can Do About Sexual Harassment In The Workplace When You Don't Want to Call The Cops, circa 1990 (Text : 28: 37)
  - Women and Law (Week 3), September 17, 1998 (Text : 28: 38)
  - Women and Law (week 4), February 24, 1998 (Text : 28: 39)
  - Women and Law (Week 5), May 5, 1998 (Text : 28: 40)
  - Women and Law (week 6), March 10, 1998 (Text : 28: 41)
  - Women and Law, March 14, 1998 (Text : 28: 42)
  - Women and Law, March 24, 1998 (Text : 28: 43)
  - Women and Law, March 31, 1998 (Text : 28: 44)
  - Women and Law (Abortion), April 23, 1998 (Text : 28: 45)